## FAJAR ABDURROHMAN

Updated 29/11/2024

+6281329493505 | abdurrohmanfajar10@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/fajar-abdurrohman | www.fajarnext.my.id | github.com/fajar2510

Ngawi, Indonesia

I am Fajar Abdurrohman, and I am very interested in applying for this job opportunity. I am currently working a side job in my village government. I have experience in IT Support or Software Development for web and mobile, also good in graphics design and 2D Animation. I am enthusiastic about the opportunity and all appreciate it.

## Work experience

Freelance - Ngawi, Indonesia	2023 - 2024

Fullstack Developer & Graphics Design

#### Dinas Ketenagakerjaan & Transmigrasi Jawa Timur - Surabaya, Indonesia

2020 - 2021

IT Support and Web Developer (Internship+Honorary)

- Developed an Interactive Geographic Mapping Web Application for the Workforce in East Java.
- Maintenance Computer and Networking.

#### Universitas Negeri Surabaya, - Surabaya, Indonesia

2017 - 2019

- Aiku Software Development as Programmer; Mobile App. Psychology Consultation
- Information System Accountant as Programmer; Finance management debit & credit.
- Information System Executive as Programmer; Blood stock management hospital.

#### CV. Linas Media Informatika - Gresik, Indonesia

2018 - 2019

Frontend Dev. Flutter

• Designed Frontend with Flutter for a food ordering Mobile App in school canteens.

#### **Education**

#### Universitas Negeri Surabaya - Surabaya, Indonesia

2017 - 2023

Master of Computers, Study program of Information Systems (S1 Sistem Informasi), GPA 3.56/4.00

- Project: Accounting Information System: Balancing debits and credits, financial reports; Psychologist Consultation Mobile App: Flutter, Firebase Auth, Chatting features; SystemInformation System: Blood stock management.
- <u>E-Journal publication</u>. Interactive Geographic Information System: Visual Mapping, Training fund allocation.

# Bootcamp, Courses, Training, & Certification

#### Relevant studies:

- Coursera Google IT Support: Networking, Computer Architecture, IT Management, Cyber Security, etc.
- Harisenin.com Bootcamp: Full Stack Developer.
- Dicoding: Cloud Google, AWS, SQL, Frontend, Backend, Network, DevOps, Machine Learning, etc.
- KOMINFO Digitalent Scholarship: <u>Graphics 2D Animation</u>. Adobe Illustrator Adobe Animate.
- Skillshare: 2D Animation, UI UX Design, Figma.
- Codecademy: Linux Command, Typescript, Javascript, Git, Github, HTML, CSS.
- Udemy: Web Developer Bootcamp (Colt Steele).

### **Skills**

Technical: Computer Maintenance, Software Development (System Analyst, Databases; Mysql; Postgresql; Maria DB,

Programming; Laravel; Codelgniter; React. js, Web Hosting Admin), and Good Typing (10 finger).

Other : Graphic Design, 2D Animation & Editing Video (Figma, Adobe Animate, Adobe Illustrator, Canva, Capcut)

Non technical: Attention to Detail, Critical Thinking, Empathy, Flexibility, Respectfulness, Organized, Teamwork.

Language: English (Intermediate, <u>TEP 546</u>), Indonesian (Native).